The difference 24hour makes.
Sean Kiryaku, how are you? How are you?
>> Than I have felt in almost two weeks.
>> Stateside.
>> Even
>> tarantula free.
>> Tarantula free. I slept with no mosquito
netting. It was pretty great.
>> Gotta love it. You know, Texas might not
be my favorite state, but it certainly
sounds better than the state you were in
before,
>> man. And I got to go back for another
what, 10 days of filming. Oh my god.
>> Oh, really?
>> And I want to tell you, too, yesterday
we left um we left. There's not even a
village. It's just us. We're the only
like structure that you can see. So the
hurricane came through the night before
and just walloped us. And so
we get in the in the suburban and Ted,
we didn't go 100 feet and the road was
just it just didn't exist anymore. It
was just gone
>> and there was this big ditch.
>> So
>> how did you get to the airport?
>> Well, the star of the movie, Jeff Fee
and I we got out of the car and um and
we took rocks. We we got big rocks to to
put enough rocks together that we could
at least at speed try to jump over this
thing with this 20-year-old Suburban,
25-year-old Suburban. We actually made
it. It's 30 miles on a dirt road and the
road just didn't exist anymore.
>> That's Afghan style with the rocks.
He he he uh is very generous with a um
he supports a an orphanage in
Afghanistan and he said the roads in
Afghanistan are way better than this.
And I said,
>> "Well, now they are."
>> Well, they are.
>> That's that's the main thing that the
United States contributed. I mean, you
know, before when I went to Afghanistan
before um you know, the the the NATO
NATO started building roads, they were
always, you know, the Afghans were
always saying, "Man, we need better
roads." Um, that's the one thing I feel
like as an American we did provide,
although we didn't provide them with
high quality roads, but because they,
you know, they buckled. There was a lot
of corruption. You know, there's a lot
of different qualities of road work and
we kind of gave them the [__] version
and they kind of needed the good version
because it's,
>> you know, there's probably no place on
earth with a higher variation in average
temperature between winter and summer
than Afghanistan.
>> I would agree with that. I mean, so it's
like that's, you know, it's like the
opposite of like say La Hoya where
there's like a 15 degree range and, you
know, it's there's no cracks on the
sidewalk because everything's kind of
perfect even if it was poured 100 years
ago.
>> So, John, there's some news. Um,
>> yeah.
>> Should we get to it? Um, let me go
through like what we're what we're going
to talk about. Um, obviously Gaza.
>> Yeah. But give us the the good, the bad,
and the ugly for everybody to hear.
>> All right. So the good well you may
about Gaza or about all of it?
>> About everything.
>> Okay, here we go. So here comes we're so
talk we got a peace we've got a makings
of a ceasefire/pace deal in Gaza. Uh
improbably but hey happily I think um
the the polling is a back on Trump's
deportation surge. Very interesting.
Basically people want illegals deported
but they don't like how Trump is doing
it. Um, Tom, this might be one of the
most disgusting stories I've ever heard
in my life. Tom Hullman, who accepted
that $50,000 bribe in a sting operation,
is being allowed to keep the money.
Never heard of such a thing. I assume
you have thoughts. Nick Sorder, what a
grifter. Um, you know, he got arrested
in Portland. He's blaming, he's saying
that the cops are being uh in uh are
basically the pawns of Antifa.
>> Infiltrated. They're infiltrated by
Antifa. Antifa has taken over the
Portland Police Department and that's
the only reason why he was arrested.
>> It's like, dude, you were like, you
should be blamed. No, the Portland
Police Department was was beating up pro
protesters and you got swept up
alongside them. This should have tipped
you over to the protesters side. Okay,
that's right. And then um interestingly
um the Department of Defense and this is
disturbing. This is like Stalinist um
has opened over 300 investigations
into its personnel for the crime of
insulting Charlie Kirk potentially. 300
investigations. The DoD has nothing
better to do. Um, and finally, and
Charlie Kirk is apparently gonna have
there's literally a bigger push to put
up statues of Charlie Kirk all over the
country than there than there has been
of any other fallen American since
Abraham Lincoln. So, you know, I mean,
you know, let's just stipulate that
Charlie Kirk was uh, you know, let's
just stipulate he was a good guy, but
was he a Lincoln? I don't know.
I'm a member of this men's group called
the HEPA, the American Helenic
Educational Progressive Association. And
every year on Memorial Day, and this is
one of many, many things we do. Mostly
we raise money for scholarships and for
medical research. But every year on
Memorial Day, the whole gang of us, it's
like a hundred of us, will meet at
Arlington Cemetery and we put wreaths on
the graves of every Greek American
veteran that's buried at Arlington.
>> Well, several of those Greek American
veterans are are Medal of Honor
recipients, and one of them is the
recipient of two Congressional Medals of
Honor.
>> Wow. There are no statues for those
guys,
>> right?
>> But Charlie freaking Kirk is gonna have
statues all over America.
>> It's insane. I mean, it's it's
definitely a fever dream. Um, if I may,
I think we should get straight into
Gaza. What do you think?
>> Yeah, agreed. We have pieces at hand,
right? Isn't that
>> pieces at hand? It looks like Look, God
bless President Trump. Good for him.
Yes.
>> I mean, so, uh, you know, you I always
like to give credit where it's due, and
it's due here. Um, it looks, John, it's
exactly like you said yesterday. The
strike against Cutter was a a bridge too
far for Trump. It angered him beyond
belief. Uh, behind behind the scenes,
basically, BB was dead to him at that
point. and he decided like I'm not
saying he's like on team Palestine, but
he wants this war over and he knows that
BB is responsible for it and I you know
it may or may not be about a Nobel Peace
Prize, but it's certainly he wants this
over. He wanted it over. Now he's just
seeing that you know BB was the
instigator and basically this thing has
to come to an end. Um so the current
deal it's really I mean this is I mean I
put this in the thumbnail this morning,
Israel humiliated. I think it has been.
I mean, let's let's imagine imagine
where we were two weeks ago where it
looked like BB was like smuggly take
thinking that all 20 points of Trump's
plan were all basically what Israel
wanted. We interpreted it that way. The
whole world did now the very first step,
right? Israel has to withdraw
completely. That's the very first step
before any hostages get released. Then
at that the next step in this in this
plan and and Israel has agreed to this.
Um well let's say let's just say this be
has agreed to it. He has to go to his to
his cabinet and we'll see if his very
fragile coalition stands together holds
together. I'm very curious to talk to
you about that. Then the second step is
hostages get released. You know they
call it 58 hostages 20 including 20
living ones. Let's call it what it is.
It's 20 people are going to be released
um and 38 bodies. the Palestinians get
back hundreds if not thousands of their
hostages being held by the Israelis. Um,
and then you for one second, let me one
second.
>> The way this has played out over the
years has been that there are like, you
know, 100 or 500 or a thousand
Palestinians for every one Israeli.
>> It's not going to be that big of a of a
difference. not as lopsided,
>> but there have been a couple of hints
that the Palestinians may be willing to
scuttle this whole deal if a certain
medical doctor
>> who's being held in an Israeli prison
isn't released and then all of a sudden
that disappeared from the media.
>> What are your thoughts about that? You
know, I I think that the Palestinians
know that basically they're in the
catbird seat now. And um and they and
and I I think this is more about like
they feel like they can exert some
pressure. Uh they know they've won, you
know, I mean, the Israelis can try to
spin it any way they want. Um you know,
it's it's interesting because truly the
Israelis have defined pirick victory.
Um, you know, you've killed a lot of
people, you flattened a lot of
territory, and you and you [__] up in
doing it. It's kind of fascinating for
students in history.
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
>> I want to add one other thing if you if
you don't mind,
>> please.
>> Uh, yesterday a publication that I never
heard of called the Middle East Monitor.
>> Oh,
>> did an article about me and it quoted
the political adviser to the Israeli
foreign minister. He said that I am an
enemy of Israel, that I am an enemy of
the Jewish people. He called me a
virulent anti-semite, which I mean, not
only is that just ridiculous. Nobody's
ever ever called me anything like that
before in my life. A virulent
anti-semite.
>> If you criticize Israel, by definition,
you're an anti-semite.
>> And that that's it. and that um that I
am an example of the intellectual rot
that has taken place, his words, taken
place on the American left.
Well, like I say, I never heard of this
publication before. It appears to be
somehow
tied, and I don't mean just
support-wise. I mean it's like formally
tied to the Israeli government.
But I think that the Israelis are very
upset with this with this deal. They
were upset with negotiations for this
deal. They were upset that Americans
have turned against them. There was a
poll on CNN, I was just watching it 15
minutes ago, saying that at the start of
this thing two years ago, um, Americans
supported Israel by 46 percentage points
over the Palestinians. today. That
number is they support the Palestinians
by one percentage point over the
Israelis. And I'm wondering if the
Israelis are going to take this slap
that is the ceasefire and they're going
to begin taking it out on individual
Americans.
>> Take it out. Taking it out on individual
Americans. How?
>> By threatening people like you and me.
by having uh Google demonetize this
show, which apparently has been done
now,
>> and um by by going after individuals who
do not tow the Zionist line on
Palestine. Well, so I don't want I don't
like to I don't want to give the Mossad
any ideas, but I think that would be
actually a pretty smart tactic on their
part because their entire existence and
their their well I should say this their
ability to thrive depends entirely on
American support which they have
completely lost. Right? I mean the
majority of American Jews which is the
biggest population of Jews in the
outside of Israel in the world now
opposes the Israeli government. I mean
that blows my mind. Okay,
>> that's right.
>> So the so the point is they've lost
America and they know and you know it
would not be a stupid move to target
some of the more effective uh articulate
voices who've been criticizing not
Israel as an idea or as a state or maybe
in some cases but specifically the way
that they act their strategies and their
tactics and their apartheid and their
abuse of the Palestinian people. Right?
So, if they can, you know, maybe the
whole idea is like, well, we've got to
get these certain Americans to shut up.
Um, and then, you know, maybe Americans
will forget what we've done. I don't
think it would work, but you know,
honestly, I don't really blame them for
trying. And we should probably bring in
Robbie to talk about what's happened
here to the show. Um,
>> uh, Robbie, let's I'm gonna pop you in
here.
>> Robbie, thanks for coming on. So, just a
little house little housekeeping just
obviously like, follow, and share the
show and all that. Um, we're doing we're
still on Rumble. Everything is great
over there. Um, but YouTube we're having
some problems with.
>> Yeah. Well, it's kind like what you just
said at the at the top. Uh, 24 hours can
bring a whole world of change. So,
before YouTube had demonetized the
channel in the middle of September, they
said because of a paperwork error.
So, we've got the paperwork error
resolved.
An hour after the paperwork error was
resolved,
YouTube has then slapped us with a
community strike about an episode that
that that Ted and John did. I think it
was last week uh talk about how
basically how Hamas has won the war,
which I hate to tell you this, they did.
So, YouTube has then has now demonetized
the channel. So keep So for those of
y'all who are think about this YouTube,
the progressive platform, the champion
of all things free speech and uh of the
and diversity, is going after two people
with a different opinion than the
approved opinion that Google has.
Meanwhile, Rumble, the right-wing echo
chamber, is financially supporting John
and Ted and allowing them to speak
freely.
Think about that for a second.
So what my So what might appeal to you
is if you want this show to continue
because John and Ted, they got bills
they got to pay. Please watch us on
Rumble.
>> Yeah,
>> Rumble is paying them. Rumble is not
throttling them. The show is growing.
Let me see. Last time I looked, just one
second, y'all. We're going to do some
live action stuff right here. a $20
donation from you from Yung Pat over on
Rumble. Thank you. Thank you.
>> Because you can't do because you can't
do anything on YouTube. You can't
donate. There's no ads. They have
completely demonetized the channel. As
of right now, we have 854 channel
followers and 29 paid subscribers. So,
thank you to each and every one of you.
>> By the way, a little um also we do have
a for people who want to donate um other
PayPal. Here's the PayPal address. D
program podcast atgmail. A little bit of
uh housekeeping here. Thank you so much
to uh Grim Music Services and Wesley uh
Jerasunus
and Killian Welts have all been generous
donors via the PayPal. Uh and we really
appreciate you guys. Thank you.
>> Yeah, for sure. And I mean that that's
really all I've got to say is know this
is not new for YouTube.
>> YouTube YouTube killed RT. YouTube
killed RT America. YouTube has
deplatformed John. I think this is what
the the second time, the third time
they've demonetized you and they've
>> a lot of conservative voices, a lot of
left voices. Anyone with a strong
opinion tends to get ousted from
YouTube.
>> And I think here's what's happened and
I'm going go away because we have a lot
of stuff we have to cover. I think the
reason for the for the crackdown, the
newest polls show that young Americans,
especially young conservative,
right-wing uh uh Republicans, if you
want to call it that, just the Gen Z
types, have turned against Israel with a
vengeance.
>> Yeah,
>> that is why they're doing this. BB
Netanyahu in his own words made an
appeal while he was in Washington DC
talking about how important the social
media wars are and how the Zionist
entity has to take control of social
media. That's why they went after Tik
Tok. That's what this is all about. This
is about censorship. This is about
throttling. This is about strangling
people's ability to make a living. And
if you support free speech, Rumbles
Rumble's the tip of the spear.
>> Thank you, Robbie. Much appreciated.
and and and Robbie is 100% correct
there. So, yeah. No, I think that we are
I think they're going after us for that.
Um, you know, we're they're going to go
after people like us. And I I think, you
know, maybe that lqar coin, by the way,
that I found on my laundry the other
day.
>> You know what, Ted? Stranger things have
happened, man.
>> Yeah,
>> stranger things have happened.
>> By the way, a little housekeeping before
I forget. So yesterday we had that angry
uh LGBT uh person about the uh Supreme
Court case. I want to just be clear
here. I'm not going to apologize, but
that person was correct. The the case
was the article that I read in the New
York Times was extremely confusing and
convoluted um about this case. the the
plaintiff is actually a an
anti-transition
anti-trans person who was uh who was
being suppressed by a law that said that
you're not allowed. So I don't want So
there's 20 states including Colorado
that don't allow um you to give advice
again to minors against tr uh
transitioning against gender affirming
surgery and and and and therapy and so
on. So this plaintiff was a conservative
um and the Supreme Court was uh but the
but the way it was written it made it
look exactly the opposite. So basically
the case is a free speech case saying I
have the right to tell kids who come to
me that they shouldn't transition don't
trans. Um and so that's what that was.
So I did misread that. I was mistaken. I
said I would look into it and if I was
wrong I would say I'm wrong. I'm wrong.
So there Apologize, Ted.
Anyway,
um all right, with that, let's get back.
So, John, this is this is big news,
though. Back in back to Gaza, right? I
mean, so
um yeah, BB Netanyahu lost everything.
It was cutter.
>> That's exactly what it was. You know,
there's there's one thing about Donald
Trump. You can't make him look weak. If
you make him look weak, you're going to
pay a price. and bombing Qatar and then
telling Trump apparently at the last
possible minute so that there was
nothing that he could do about it. That
was too much. It was too much for Trump
to take and and he slapped him down.
>> I don't blame him.
>> I don't either.
>> Not at all. No, I mean and and I don't
blame the cutteries for being angry
about it either. All right. So the
question now be So does Netanyahu's
government survive?
>> Well, you know what? I hate to say yes,
but the only reason that I say yes is
because there's literally no alternative
except one that might be even further to
the right,
>> right? It's like, well, it's it's like
here's the thing, right? BB, you know,
is having this meeting perhaps right now
while we're talking
>> in Tel Aviv where he's going to be like,
listen, guys, it's like you guys can
dream of greater Israel all you want and
we've already got 60% of the West Bank.
We probably aren't going to have to give
any if not or most of that back. But but
Gaza, we're never going to annex it.
It's gone forever. We overreached. The
whole world hates us. Get real. You
think you can do this without me and
send me to prison? Try, but you can't
form You can't form a government without
me. That's what that's going to be his
case. Yeah. I don't know if it'll
prevail or not. I have no idea. But,
>> you know, I don't I don't know if these
if the right-wing parties can form a
coalition. I don't know where they would
find I don't know where they would find
the the votes to to form a government.
>> You know, see, that's the other thing. I
was having a conversation with a friend
of mine last night who just happens to
be Jewish. And I said, um,
>> even though you're an anti-semite, does
he know,
>> right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I Right. I
secretly I must hate him or something.
Yeah. So I said the the the problem that
the Israeli government has is that it's
the same problem that the Greek
government used to have where you've
got, you know, 36 political parties, all
of them get elected to parliament. You
can't possibly form a a government that
is going to be strong enough to last its
entire term. So what the Greeks did is
they raised the threshold to enter
parliament from 3% to 5%. that knocked
out a bunch of these parties that that
were only, you know, that were only um
uh based around one person anyway, you
know, one charismatic person. So 3% to
5% and then they passed this this law
that changed everything. If you are the
party that comes in first, you get an
extra 50 seats
>> and 50 seats is always enough to form an
actual government.
enter in any coalition with anybody
else.
>> That's a smart system right now. I bet I
bet Emanuel Mcron had a wish that France
had that system.
>> Seriously.
>> Um John uh Fuso, thanks for the donation
is asking over and under how many days
after Hamas releases all the hostages
will Israel renegotiate and start
genociding again? Look, that's a good
question because as the Hamas
spokesperson said yesterday, Israel has
a long uh has a long history of not
abiding by signed agreements and uh
reneging on ceasefires and everything.
That's going to be what they want to do.
So, this really boils down to what does
add Donald Trump, how long is his
attention span on this? Is he going to
keep an eye like on BB and and or is he
gonna like drift off and start ranting
about Charlie Kirk statues or something?
Well, if he's serious, and you know, we
chuckle about it, but if he's serious
about winning the Nobel Peace Prize,
>> he is not gonna let BB Netanyahu wreck
that for him. Not a chance.
>> Um,
well, the Sim Simon Noski says from
Quebec, "Fuck Zionist Israel." Agree.
Um, Fuso also says, "Thanks for another
donation. Charlie Kirk is mega Jesus."
That's exactly what he
>> Yes, he is. We've got the commemorative
coin now that's been proposed in the
House of Representatives.
>> The Jace Show is asking
>> is questioning me. I know that's
hilarious, right? Um is calling me out.
I'm curious how the Gazins have won if
Tony Blair is going to be running the
place. It seems like ethnic cleansing is
still on the table.
>> Tony Blair is not going to be running
the place. It it that's over. That's not
true. Um this is I mean and look I think
John I think what we're looking at here
and it's a very these are the early
early days right so everything I say
should be taken with like a salt lick of
salt but I think what we're looking at
is an Ireland solution here where Hamas
will basically remain in charge in the
same way that the IRA basically
demilitarized and became
Shinfane right I think that Hamas they
might be rebranded. They might rename
themselves, but basically the same guys
who are Hamas are going to be running
the Gaza Strip for the foreseeable
future. They may give up a number of
their weapons. They may agree to put all
of their weapons into an arsenal. They
may agree to convert their soul their
their soldiers into police officers. But
I think basically that the facts on the
ground can't change because they are the
power structure that maintains law and
order and have been for 15 years. I I
don't I just don't see I think it's a
fantasy this stuff about like Trump Gaza
hotel and you know I mean there could be
a Trump Gaza hotel but it's not like
it's going to be ma you know the Gaza
Strip is going to be maintained by the
United States and like this coalition
and like with Tony Blair and that
they're all going to grift and I I just
don't I don't think so.
>> Yes. Yes. I I agree. I agree.
You know the thing here too, I know
we're pressed for time. There are so
many things to talk about, but I want to
say real quickly the Israelis for the
for for this to not happen again, the
Israelis need to learn a lesson. And the
lesson is very simple.
You do not slaughter innocent people.
You do not deny people basic human
rights. Martin Luther King famous
>> and gloat about it.
>> Gloat about it. That's right. Martin
Luther King famously said that that we
should never underestimate a man's
desire to be free and Gaza was the
biggest open air prison in the world.
And yeah, I mean the mis I mean look,
let's be real here. I mean, the the
world never should have tolerated the
way things were in Gaza before 2023. Um,
but you know, afterwards it just tipped
into it couldn't be ignored. Um, so
JRock 952 basically, [__] you. But
here's what he said. John's probably a
Holocaust denier. I mean, he is a
truther after all.
>> [__] idiot. I'm neither a truther nor
a Holocaust denier. [__] idiot. And
if he knew anything about me or watched
anything that I've done, he would know
that.
>> Yeah. I I hate it when people just sort
of say [__] on the internet just like
>> Yeah. Like this [__] who uh who wrote
the article about me in this
publication. I can't even remember the
name now. Middle East something. Um, one
of the comments was that I'm stupid,
morbidly obese, and ugly, too, on top of
it. And that
>> Yeah, and your mommy's fat, too. Um, any
any chance the Egyptians Houdini wants
to know, the Egyptians will be involved
with Gaza internal security?
>> It's a good question. Israelis over the
years have asked the go the Egyptians to
to get more uh involved which is ironic
because Egypt used to administer Gaza.
That's correct. As back in the day
before the 67 war the Egyptians want
nothing to do with Gaza.
>> It is nothing but trouble.
>> Uh they don't have enough food and jobs
for their own people and they don't want
to take this on as well.
>> Yeah. I I think they they're content
with just being neighbors here. Um,
I like this comment. Tammy Land Landan
says, "This is why I, as a lifelong
Democrat, realize we were better off
with Trump after all was said and done."
You know, look, I I totally see that
argument. I mean, look, the best thing
about Donald Trump is he doesn't seem to
like stupid wars. And um you know, I
mean, he does a lot of things that I
disagree with, like blowing up
Venezuelan boats, but this is a great ex
like if this goes through, if this
works, who's going to be able to argue
that we would have been better off under
Kla Harris? I mean, this is a major
major issue. I mean, yeah, I mean, I
care about healthcare. I care about a
lot of other stuff. But I mean, the
United States was actively participating
in the mass murder of tens if not
hundreds of thousands of people and
contributing to the misery of untold
more. Um, you know, I mean, if Donald
Trump brings an puts an end to this,
great.
Yeah. Great. Great. This isn't about
personalities. Whether we hate Donald
Trump or love Donald Trump, it's about
bringing human rights to the
Palestinians.
>> Precisely.
Uh Sean, should we move on to some of
these other topics?
>> Yeah.
>> What do you want to talk about?
>> Oh man, much today.
>> There's Tom Holman.
>> Yeah, let's talk about him. He He gets
to keep his money, which is like right
out of bizarro world uh of of US
juristprudence. I don't freaking
understand it at all.
>> He should have been fired. He's caught
like basically dead to rights accepting
a $50,000 bribe in an FBI sting
operation, he pocketed the 50k and
literally
>> he's like so [__] shameless
>> that he like, you know, instead of just
like turning it back over right away
like my bad, thank you for not
prosecuting me. Thank you for not firing
me. You know, thank you. Thank you. He's
like pock he's keeping it and the
government's letting him keep it. I mean
this is a whole new level of of
shamelessness. I think I mean I think
it's a I think it's depraved honestly.
You know it it is depraved. And another
thing too is
it it just gives you such a clear
example of the corruption of our um of
our justice system where if they want to
go after you and silence you, it's easy.
Uh if they want to give you the right to
do anything your heart desires, that's
easy, too. There is a great book um
that's been out for many years. I've
recommended it a hundred times called
three felonies a day and uh it's written
by a Harvard law professor who argues
that that
we are so over legislated and so over
criminalized in this country that the
average person on the average day going
about his or her normal business commits
three felonies every single day.
>> That's awesome.
>> So if they want
Yeah, they're going to get you. There's
nothing you can do to protect.
>> Is it Berea who supposed the NKVD guy
from the Soviet Union who supposedly
said you you show me the man, I'll show
you the crime.
>> That's exactly what he said. Yes.
>> Um, by the way, we're number 11 on
Rumble nationally. Just saying right now
as we speak.
>> Um, so let's got an ad. You've probably
noticed Rumble is growing fast and it's
not slowing down. They're building a
real alternative to big tech that puts
creators first and actually protects
free speech. And now there's Rumble
Premium, an easy way to upgrade your
experience. With premium with premium,
you get ad free viewing across the
platform. No pre-rolls, no
interruptions, just the content you came
for. Plus, premium members unlock
exclusive content like bonus videos,
behind the scenes drops, and more from
your favorite creators. Right now,
Rumble is offering $10 off on annual
subscriptions. Just go to
rumble.com/premium and use the promo
code studio at checkout. That's
rumble.com/premium.
Promo code studio no ads more freedom
and content you actually care about
that's the deal u funny funny comment
that I should about from fuzo thanks
another donation you guys are actually
breijit macron penis deniers
I am a I am a breij macron penis desire
denier I think that on the extremely
unlikely event I ever got to see her
bits there would be no penis there would
not be a crying game situation
confident.
>> I feel confident that's the case. I do
not believe
>> Breijit Mcronone is a man. I believe
she's a hideous woman.
>> She was She was never Yeah. She was
never beautiful.
>> No.
>> Um but she's very put together. She's
French. She's stylish. You know,
>> I got to talk about Nick Sord. Is is it
Sorter or Storur? I don't even know.
>> I I don't know to tell you the truth.
>> I don't know either. And and to tell you
the truth, I mean, I never really
thought of about this guy at all. I had
seen him on Fox many times before. He's
a street reporter for Fox, right? They
sent him to There's been all these
demonstrations outside of the Portland
ICE office. Um, which by the way, mainly
there's been more demonstrations because
basically it's so hilarious. Not much
was going on there at all. There were
tiny little protests there from time to
time. So the Trump administration since
sent the National Guard out there and
and basically to to protect the ICE
office. Um so that provoked actual
protests to come out to say because they
were against the National Guard being in
Portland, right?
>> And so there was a a little of a of a
frackus the other day. Um and the um and
so Nick was got basically got uh roughed
up and arrested by the uh Portland PD
despite having press credentials. This
kind of thing happens from time to time
to reporters when they're on the street
covering protests. Why does it happen?
Because cops don't give a [__] if you're
a reporter. When cops go into an arrest
frenzy for demon for demonstrators, they
sweep everyone else and they don't
really like reporters anyway. And so
even though they see the press badge,
they just don't care. That's what
happened to Nick. Nick, you should, you
know, do tell the truth and become a
good leftist like like me. But instead,
he's going out spinning this saying that
the Portland PD has become corrupt
puppets of violent Antifa thugs. and he
was arrested because of, you know,
somehow they were doing the bidding of
Antifa even while they were arresting
supposed Antifa. I mean,
>> this is embarrassing.
>> You know, listen, as a regular on Fox
News, I'm going to tell you that they
every show on that network is going to
run with this.
>> It's really It's really though. It has a
z it's it's negative credibility, right?
It's that line that I always like to use
from my lawyer. Not only is that not
true, it can't be true. It's it's
ridiculous.
>> Radical left pro- Antifa police
department of Portland, Oregon,
committed crimes against humanity when
they arrested our colleague.
I I it writes itself.
>> Yeah. It's like basically Nick, they
treated you like you were a reporter for
for Jake for a jackabin. Okay, that's
what happened. Uh all you know,
basically they didn't care that you were
from Fox. You didn't get a paper
dispensation. You were, you know, they
they were thugs to you because you were
a journalist.
>> I mean, it's so I mean, honestly, I
don't even get why they're going why why
he and they are going with this. I would
have just been like, "We just we just
won't talk about that."
>> Exactly.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Because it goes against our our
narrative. Why not just shut up?
>> Why not just shut up? Yes.
>> It's it Okay, so while we're at this.
All right. So, listen. We got to I guess
Charlie Kirk's never made more news than
since getting killed. and um Charlie.
So, right now the Department of Defense,
which is supposed to be protecting us
and and our national security interests
around the globe, is spending
god knows how many resources, launching
300 internal investigations
into employees, in other words,
soldiers, airmen, sailors, god knows who
else because the Pentagon is the biggest
employer on earth. um like trying to
looking for people who said mean stuff
about Charlie Kirk on the internet.
Setting aside the fact that probably
some of those people will be found not
guilty.
What the [__] is going on, John? I mean,
this is Does this make any sense to you
at all? I mean, what is this? It's a
loyalty test.
>> It is. It's some kind of a crazy
misguided loyalty test. When when I woke
up this morning, I I popped on the news
like I do every morning. I just flipped
through the the channels and I happened
to stumble on a on a a response to a
question that Donald Trump was giving
yesterday
where he said that um he had decided to
reban
flag burning. He said the courts have
never been clear on this which is 1,000%
not true
>> except for the United States Bush
administration. The Supreme Court ruled
unequivocally that flag burning flag
burning is a protected
uh political statement. It's protected
by the first amendment constitution. And
he said that he is going to reban flag
burning because flag burning leads to
horrific violence which is what the
radical left wants to do and blah blah
blah. Um this Charlie Kirk thing is is
in the exact same vein. We're being told
now what we can believe and what we
can't believe, what we can do and what
we can't do. It's dangerous, even if
it's temporary because it's going to
have to wind its way through the courts
again like it always does
>> and it's going to ruin some careers and
some lives.
>> Yes, it will.
>> Um, let me let me give you give you some
quotes from the Washington Post here.
Right. So, um, Pentagon spokesman Sean
Parnell wrote on social media. He's the
spokesman for the DoD. It's a
criticizing Charlie Kirk or mocking
Turning Point USA is a violation of the
oath. It's conduct unbecoming. It's a
betrayal of the Americans they've sworn
to protect and dangerously incompatible
with military service. Those in our
ranks who rejoice at an act of domestic
terrorism are unfit to serve the
American people.
He also, by the way, this is this um so
Hegsath laughed about the attack on Paul
Pelosi.
>> Yeah, he did.
>> Asked about this. Parnell, the spokesman
said, "The situation isn't the same. An
American was assassinated. We will not
tolerate military or civilian personnel
who celebrate or mock the assassination
of a fellow American.
>> I gotta say Paul Pelosi came close to
being assassinated. Yeah, he did.
>> Um I mean that the guy went beat the
[__] out of him with a hammer.
>> With a hammer.
>> He's an old dude.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so I mean talk about Sopa Street,
right? I mean,
>> I'll say
>> so. Yeah. 158 non-uniformed personnel
have been investigated as of September
30th, including 27 civilian defense
department civilians. Two have been
removed from employment.
>> Jeez.
I mean, this is not, you know, a this is
a this is really really crazy. So under
article 88 of the uniform code of
military justice, a serviceman or
service woman can be prosecuted for
contemptuous words against their
military or civilian leaders or against
elected officials, but not against, you
know, private citizens like Charlie
Kirk.
This is I mean this is a this is this is
a form of madness. And I guess
I'm laughing because I'm I know the
answer already.
>> Ridiculous. Would it be too much to
expect some Democrat to stand up and say
enough already with the Charlie Kirk
[__]
No Democrat
in either the House or the Senate or any
Democratic governors, not a single one
has the balls to do that.
Not a single one.
>> That's what I thought.
>> No.
>> [__] insane. You know, listen, I
>> I'm so sorry that this happened to
Charlie Kirk. This is a terrible,
terrible thing. It shouldn't have
happened to anybody.
>> 100%.
>> The guy has little kids at home. It it
No one should be killed for their
beliefs.
>> Yeah.
>> But he's just a guy.
>> He's not a god.
>> He's not the president who saved the
nation.
>> Let's move on.
No, no, no, no, he's not. Um,
and then we should talk about I guess we
should talk about Charlie Kirk's
statues. So,
one day after Charlie Kirk died, more
than a dozen House rep Republicans um
sent out a letter calling for a statue
of Charlie Kirk at the US capital. A
week later, Oklahoma lawmakers
introduced a bill that would require
every state university in Oklahoma to
every single one to put up a Charlie
Kirk statue in a dedicated square or
plaza. Texas State Rep. uh Nate
Shatzline called for similar legislation
in that state. The new College of
Florida, which I've spoken at, used to
be a nice lefty school, uh, but it's g
been completely taken over by Ronda
Santis and purged of progressives, uh,
announced that it is commissioning a
Kirk statue and shared an AI version of
what it would look like. Uh, they say
they have a bunch of artists who are
willing to look for it um to uh to to uh
to bid on the on the deal. Um, so
basically it looks like there's going to
be a a massive amount of Kirk statues
all over the United States. So this is
great. I love this quote, right?
Reflect. So Kirk Savage is an art
historian at University of Pittsburgh,
which is a very important school related
to art. Um, and he's written about
public monuments. He said, "The only
real precedent I can think of in terms
of the speed of all this and the call
for more statues is Abraham Lincoln,
um, whose assassination was followed by
swift calls for statues. Um, the morning
after, a formerly enslaved woman named
Charlie Scott was said to have donated
$5, which was a lot of money, to a
monument to the to President Lincoln.
link uh eventually leading to
Freriedman's memorial in DC which shows
a black man leaning next to uh to to
Lincoln. Um but anyway, this is just um
of all the people I mean of all the
people it's it's just amazing to me.
>> Rush Limba has to be spinning in his
grave. Where are the statues to Rush
Limba? That's what I'd like to know.
>> Well, I mean he and he'd kind of have a
good point. I mean,
>> you know, you think so?
>> He was a lot more important than Charlie
Kirk ever was.
>> Yes.
>> Although, you know, he was a bit of a
fraud.
>> Yeah. You know, that episode,
>> he wasn't really a conservative.
>> Was not conservative. That episode of
Family Guy where they mock him and he
says that it was all an act was actually
>> It was all an act.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, here I mean, yeah. Someone who
knew him very well told me that
basically um it was just a grift.
basically he had learned uh he had
basically sused out in the uh in the 80s
that that was the direction of talk
radio um to go conservative and he just
basically you know I mean there's a lot
of people like that in in politics who
don't believe a [__] word that they
say I don't know I mean I just don't
experience politics that way John I mean
for me it's like I believe what I
believe I can't imagine it you know
being like like an like a movie actor
like going out and thing like these
lines that I don't believe. I mean, it
would just be depressing to me. I I I'd
rather just do something else. I mean,
I'll stock shelves at, you know, at a
supermarket. I I just I just couldn't. I
I I mean, I don't really I'm not morally
looking down on someone who does that.
But it's very I don't get it. I don't
get the psychology of someone who would,
you know, stridently day after day after
day express opinions about, you know,
the way the world ought to be that you
actually don't believe.
>> Believe what kind of legacy do you leave
when you do something like that
>> and just to make money?
>> Just to make money. Like what what a
cheap grift.
>> Yeah, it really is. I mean, you're you
know, you're you're really selling your
soul for like there's not enough money.
There just isn't,
>> you know, and
the the books. It's the It's not just
the the radio show. The the books that
were ghostritten for him that he put his
that he put his name on. Every time
there was a national issue, uh, every
time there was a presidential election,
he would have one of his ghost writers
jin up a quick book and, uh, and make
more and more and more and more money on
that. It was very cynical. very very
cynical.
>> John, you got a personal request. This
is a very personal request from Sir
Bikes a Lot. Thanks for the donation,
Sir Bikes. Uh, please tell Joe Rogan
tonight. You're going on. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> And other newbies to Texas to to drive
70 miles an hour on the ramp to the
freeway. I live in San Antonio and I'm
tired of newbies driving 45 onto the
freeway.
>> You know what? Done.
I I love 70 mph speed limits. They're 80
miles an hour in Montana, parts of North
Dakota. I love it. I once got caught
going 80 in a 25 in outside of Sturgeis,
South Dakota. This is like five years
ago. 80 and a 25. The cop could not
apologize enough for stopping.
>> Like, you know, because if it was 60,
I'd say, "Buddy, just slow down." But,
you know, 80
it it it it stays in the radar gun in
the memory and somebody could call me on
it. And he I'm so sorry, sir. I I'm I'm
going to have to write you a ticket. And
I'm like, I'm so sorry. I was I mean, 80
miles an hour in a 25. I didn't realize
it was a 25. I had just come off the
highway.
>> Oh [__]
>> He could not apologize enough. So, I
just went in to the courthouse in
Sturgis the next day and I paid the
fine. It was $225.
>> You got off easy.
>> I sure did. I mean, they
>> You know, I don't know if this is still
true, but my old roommate Chris was um
arrested for driving 20 over the speed
limit in North Carolina. They told him
that they had to arrest him under North
Carolina law. You know, in the South,
the wiggle room is really like four
miles an hour over the state limit,
right? In, you know, up north it's it's
definitely 12 is the magic number. cops
will tell you 13, you know, keep it at
12, you'll you'll be okay. 13 keep it at
nine.
>> And yeah, I feel like 10 is exactly the
number, especially if you look at the
ticket, right? Because it's increments
of 1 to five, six to 10. So if you're at
exactly a 10, you're probably not going
to get pulled over at all. Um, but my my
worst ticket, John, and this is I'm not
bragging here. I was 16 years old. I was
late to school. Uh, so I was I was go
and I had a great car and I got clock
pulled over going 115 in the school zone
in front of my school. Um, and
there were like three cops pulled me
over. The principal saw me. I walked and
I was like I was on my third late and I
was going to be suspended. I walked in
the principal's office and he goes,
"This one's a freebie. I saw I saw you.
I I I know right from my window. I had
to pay, this was 1979, I had to pay
$465.
Um, it was a [__] [__] ton of money.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, and fortunately I had the money
because I worked like ridiculous jobs,
but I was like a [__] bat out of
hell. I mean, the the it was just a
great car. It was a had a custom V V8
Corvette engine.
>> Like,
>> oh my god. Uh, Frasmatas, how do we go
from 400,000 to 6 million dead? Why is
Holocaust revisionism so controversial?
Is it because it's highly illegal in
Europe? Not to lecture anyone, but why
not deny their narrative? Um, I'm pretty
convinced that the at least 6.8 million
Jews were killed in the Holocaust. I've
read so much about it. My my my
bookshelves are groaning with books
about the Holocaust. And when you
consider everyone, right, like basically
that was a plurality. When you consider
all the priests, the resistance members,
the Soviet soldiers, the gays, the
handicapped, the mentally ill,
>> you're really close to 25 million
people. Um I mean, I'm sorry. I mean,
>> well, you know, just in Greece
>> Holocaust revisionism,
>> just just Greek Jews
and and Greece was one of the small
countries that was 200,000 right there.
I mean the Germans kept ex you know
exquisite records I mean for the time
and we captured a lot of them. The
Soviets have those records. You can go
look at those records in the in the
Russian archives. I mean, it's really
and there's there's a book called KL,
which is uh I would recommend for
anybody who's thinking about who's
tempted by Holocaust revisionism that
just sort of details in exquisite
grinding detail, every mass killing at
every camp, every pit, you know,
everything. And you you'll you know, the
numbers are the numbers are actually a
little low, you know,
>> that wouldn't surprise me.
um that wouldn't surprise me. And you
know, in even in Roads, the island where
my grandparents come from, and I'm sorry
if I'm wasting time, um it wasn't just
it wasn't just the Jews. I mean,
certainly they rounded up all of the
Rhodian Jews, 2,000 Rodian Jews, and um
14 survived the war. But even my cousin
Mike, my dad's first cousin, uh was shot
right through the stomach uh during or
by a by a Nazi officer only because he
wasn't moving quickly enough getting the
Nazi a glass of water.
>> Yeah, they were they were like that.
They everybody
>> and not to mention like the reprisals
where they cap where like they they
catch they'd keep civilians and or they
have a list of civilians and if a German
soldier was killed in France it was the
rule was they would kill 50 local
civilians for every German soldier
killed a hundred for every officer. Um
Fuso says Antifa is equivalent to a
violent flash mob dance action. There's
no structure organization. It's a
Morpheus and an idea. Correct. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Uh that is exactly correct and thanks
for the donation. The Kirk stories that
are interesting says real real don't get
discussed. The assassin's family don't
think he's guilty saying the text
messages are fake. FD FBI hiding video
evidence that goes against their story.
I don't know about that.
Um I mean it certainly it looks right
now like the government is has their
case. Um, let's see. Uh, before July
13th, Rasmataz says CNN decided not to
air Trump rallies that day. They had so
many cameras on him and in HD. I don't
know. Um,
oh, please educate Rogan on the
difference between liberals and
leftists. I like that.
>> Oh, that's a good one.
>> The right always conflate them, blaming
the left for lib nonsense. True.
that that's always that can't be done
enough.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's talk about deportations, John. And
we're we're running low on time. I don't
want to not talk about this because I
think it's an important issue.
>> Um so obviously we're not going to get
So um the polls basically show this is
super interesting to me. Um thatif this
is the New York Times Sienna College
poll 54% of voters are in favor of
deporting undocumented people from the
United States. But 53%
think that the process isn't fair. Uh
ins snaring American citizens.
Obviously, no one's going to say that
that's fair. Uh parents of American
children and uh vendors who are, you
know, working hard and peacefully uh in
places like Chicago and Washington DC.
So, I love this story, John, because
it's a it's it's it really kind of goes
to something that we don't talk about
much in our politics. People love they
like a policy, but how you enforce that
policy matters.
And
>> Amen.
>> And so if they Go ahead.
>> Sorry. I I'm biased. I'm biased because
many members of my family came to this
country as illegal immigrants or what
are being called illegal immigrants. All
they wanted to do was work. They were
very happy to pay taxes. All they wanted
to do was to make money and send back to
their to their families. They were
starving starving back in Greece um
during and before the Second World War.
So I feel kind of a kinship to a lot of
people. Now, I don't want Venezuelan
rapists and murderers walking the
streets anymore than anybody else does,
but this wholesale deportation of people
who are just easy to grab off the street
or people who have green cards, valid
green cards, and are snatched coming out
of a courthouse or out of an immigration
office. That's not what the American
people wanted. or target or targeting
people specifically because for example
they're pro Gaza or pro Palestinian.
>> Exactly.
I think, you know, so I think that's
going to be like um, you know, a
takeaway when we finally get a
presidential historian who does a good
job um, on the Trump administrations.
Um, they're going to, you know, I think
they're going to come back and say like
Trump was on to a lot, you know, in
terms of like, you know, domestic
priorities over foreign uh, adventurism.
Most Americans were behind that. um the
idea of open borders. Most Americans
were against that because open borders
are by definition stupid and we kind I
know that's a right-wing talking point,
open borders, but they were open. I
mean,
>> it's true. They're right.
>> And so like but how you decide to
enforce a law or a rule, it's it's to
the crux of it, right? So imagine if
they'd gone about this with finesse and
like no ice goons all wrapped up in
masks and stuff and but like they start
with like the the the scumbags criminals
in the worst felons in our in our
prisons, right?
>> Get rid of those [__] We don't who
cares? We don't need them here. They're
Why are we paying for their for their
imprisonment? Send them home. If they if
the their home countries don't want to
imprison them, whatever. That's neither
here nor there. It's like and then just
sort of work through people who are
perhaps accused of heinous crimes, throw
them out of the country, go down a list
of priorities, you know, and and
certainly don't target don't don't seem
don't even appear to be punishing people
who are expressing political opinions. I
think this policy would be pretty
popular.
>> Yeah. And you know, another thing too is
there's no differentiation anymore
between sort of the
the approved immigrants and the
unapproved. Like for example, Cubans
used to be special people.
>> Oh, right.
>> Any Cuban, welcome to America. Did you
see day before yesterday that the head
of Cubans for Trump
was grabbed and is being deported?
>> That's [__] hilarious to me. Yeah.
Cubans were a special class.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Look at look at the Mario boat
lift, right? I mean, they were illegal
immigrants. All of them.
>> All of them.
>> And um you know, we but we took them in.
Yeah. We had to put them in, you know,
they were in those camps for a little
while, but not for long. Yeah. and uh
and they were you know they and they got
great benefits. Um we should wrap things
up but uh it's always a pleasure. Um
congratulations honestly to the to the
Trump administration. I hope you keep
your eye on the ball
>> and keep going. This could be huge.
>> Yeah. And it's it's the timing is really
interesting right at the at the second
anniversary of the October 7th attacks.
Um anyway, praying for the people of
Palestine. Hope that that things work
out there. Uh, we will be back tomorrow,
9:00
a.m. Eastern time. Tonight, John's on
the Joe Rogan show. What time is that?
>> Um, going on at 1 at 1 to 4. They
usually release them the next day. They
told me that that's probably what
they're going to do. It should be
tomorrow.
>> I don't know.
>> Sometime sometime tomorrow. Well, so
that'll we'll we will have talked here
before that. So, you might have more
information by then. We're here Monday
through Friday, 9 to5. If you feel like
donating, we could really desperately
use it. especially with what YouTube the
way YouTube is targeting us right now.
Send uh send a your donation to dprogram
podcast@gmail.com or if you're on live
on Rumble, you can always do it through
Rumble. Thank you everyone and see you
tomorrow, John. Have a good show. Break
a leg.
>> Thanks buddy. Bye bye.